Contact

rebecca.bing2011@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rebeccabingaman-06131b94 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Hospitals
Healthcare
Government

Rebecca Bingaman

BSN, RN, CNOR

Medford, Oregon Area

Summary

Currently a full time MBA student at Northwest Christian University. Registered Nurse with 12 years of experience (5 in emergency department/7 in operating room). I earned my ADN in 2008, BSN from Oregon Health and Science University in 2009, and Certified Nurse in the Operating Room (CNOR) in January, 2016. Retired April 1, 2018, from the US Navy Reserves as a Chief Petty Officer with 21 years of service (13 years US Navy/8 Years US Army). Skilled in Customer Service, Government, Hospitals, Healthcare, and Leadership. Strong military and protective services professional. Deployed to Afghanistan in 2012 in support of Operation Enduring Freedom at the NATO Role 3, Multinational Medical Unit.

Experience

Northwest Christian University Graduate Student May 2020 - Present (3 months) Eugene, Oregon, United States

invalid18215534
Operating Room Nurse
December 2017 - May 2020 (2 years 6 months)
Travel

Travel RN

LRS Healthcare
Travel RN
December 2017 - December 2019 (2 years 1 month)
Everywhere

US Navy Reserve 13 years 2 months Chief Petty Officer March 2005 - April 2018 (13 years 2 months)

Springfield, Oregon

Retired

Chief Petty Officer

December 2011 - October 2012 (11 months)

Afghanistan

Overseas deployment Operation Enduring Freedom/Noble Eagle

Asante

Staff Registered Nurse

August 2014 - December 2017 (3 years 5 months)

Grants Pass, Oregon

Staff Nurse/ Circulator

Grants Pass Surgery Center Llc

Staff RN

April 2013 - August 2014 (1 year 5 months)

Grants Pass, Oregon

Staff Nurse/ Circulator

Asante

Staff Registered Nurse

March 2011 - April 2013 (2 years 2 months)

Grants Pass, Oregon

Emergency Department RN (military deployment December 2011 to October

2012)

Mercy Medical Center

Staff Registered Nurse

June 2009 - April 2011 (1 year 11 months)

Roseburg, Oregon

Emergency Department

Roseburg VAMC

RN VALOR

May 2008 - June 2009 (1 year 2 months)

Roseburg, Oregon

VA Learning & Opportunities Residency

Education

Northwest Christian University

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Management · (2020 - 2022)

Oregon Health and Science University
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2005 - 2009)

Umpqua Community College ADN, Nursing Education · (2005 - 2008)